Music Plays Where am I?
I wasn't even looking.
Am I safe in here?
What the hell is wrong with you psychos?
Ow, I've been waiting for you.
Dear Nami and Robin, how are you?
I hope this finds you well.
I do so look forward to
seeing the two of you again.
I'm certain that when the time comes,
we'll be better friends than ever before.
Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there.
Hold on for me!
On this long journey that
we've only barely begun.
Friendship, love, courage
and a little bit of fun.
These are the things that
even as the years go by?
Will not ever vanish from our minds.
We are all pieces of
a single planet Earth.
Little by little we can
find each other's worth.
And as we see what sort of
form we're meant to take?
All of us know the wind will
always keep on blowing away.
Feel the wind, feel it surround you.
As you finish what you've begun.
Look through that wind
to dry All the tears as
you're breathing The
things you must overcome.
Join the quest, join the adventure.
Found in meeting somebody new.
We'll never stop for anything!
Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there.
Hold on for me.
All the tears you shed will help
you to become so much stronger.
All the tears you shed
will help you to remember.
Everything, everything, everything.
Now and forever?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, yay!
Feel the wind, feel it surround you.
As you finish what you've begun.
Look to that wind to dry all the tears.
As you're braving the
things you must overcome.
Join the quest, join the adventure.
Found new meaning, somebody new.
We'll never stop for anything!
Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there.
Hold on for me.
I wanted you and Luffy to grow up
and be marines like your granddad.
But hopes be damned, you both
turned out to be hoodlums.
Notorious, dangerous ones at that.
I'm sure you heard about what
your brother's been up to.
Now I don't expect us
to get along perfect.
But challenging the
world government head-on
and wrecking up Annie's
lobby is over the line.
By the way, I told the
little punk about his father.
Of course the news took him by
surprise can't blame the boy.
Our fathers to hell with
them and to help with
you if you ever thought
we could be Marines.
We've both got the blood of
criminals flowing through our veins.
And that was the only gift
those bastards ever gave us.
I took the name Portgas from my
mother because I owe her so much.
But I don't owe my father a damned thing.
I don't even remember the bastard.
He can keep his name.
I know, I know.
But the man tried. He wanted to...
Enough, all right?
Listen to me.
You're worth too much.
To die in a place like this!
Don't fight it.
Run wild! With us.
Our flag will be yours.
And I will call you my son.
Whitebeard is my only father.
Got it, old man.
Admiral Momonga, I've
spotted a pirate ship.
Do you know who it belongs to?
Well, the flag does look familiar.
I'll look into it.
Well, if you don't recognize them,
then they can't be anyone important.
Just leave them be.
We can't be bothered.
Not right now, at least. Sir!
that sea king is huge what if it attacks
he'd eat the whole ship
in one bite and that'd
be the end of us just
stay over there it's
gone you know we came
all this way but now we
what what are we supposed to do what can
we do come on alvida you have a plan right
Don't ask me.
It's your idea.
You're the geniuses that spent
all our money on an Eternal pose.
Don't act like I'm the one
who dragged you out here.
Well, of course.
But still, we can't just
leave Buggy and Impel down.
As his crew, we gotta go
save him. Poor Captain.
Look around you.
We're about to enter the Calm Belt.
That's the same as sailing
into a nest of sea kings.
You think this ship is ready for that?
Of course,
there is one other way
for us to get there,
but that's reserved for the Navy vessels.
We're a pirate ship.
The Gates of Justice won't
be open for people like us.
You're kidding me.
I thought breaking him
out was the hard part.
And now this?
Now we find out we can't
even get to the place.
He and his buddy Ace are gonna be killed.
We gotta help somehow.
This would never work.
Don't kid yourself.
You can't break in or out of the greatest
prison in the whole world better.
For us to quit while we're still ahead,
Back the clown had a good run but I'm
afraid his luck as a pirate has run out.
I refuse to accept it.
He's a man among men.
The only way Captain Buggy can
go out is in a blaze of glory.
Our captain's not going anywhere,
especially not the grave.
Until he finds Captain John's
Treasure Island, that's final.
And until that date comes,
we're sticking with him.
I'm gonna take the big top and
get the hell out of this place.
You guys can use a life raft or something.
How could you this is
Captain buggy ship not yours?
Well, I don't see buggy anywhere. Do you?
No, I guess not.
I'm not going to march
to Death's doorstep.
And as for this ship, I
won't let you waste it.
Those conditions aside,
if you want to rescue Buggy on
your own, then I won't stop you.
But I'll be frank, boys.
You're not going to last
five minutes in those waters.
Captain!
Thank you for everything,
but this is farewell!
Your dream will live on,
in our hearts at least.
Have a peaceful execution.
Maybe it'll be fun.
See you in the next slam, Captain.
I feel your grief, Richie.
There's no shame in sadness.
This is Momonga, Marine Code G100660.
We'll be sailing on the current
shortly, so prepare to open the gate.
The Navy ship Luffy and Hancock are on is
approaching the tub
current used exclusively
by the Navy to travel between three of
the world government's central facilities.
Just let me die!
Hey, new guy.
You don't get to eat until you pay
your respects to the cell leader.
Them's the rules around here.
What, you want me to do a little curtsy
every time I take a bite out of something?
I want you to give your
food to the boss so
I don't have to pound
your sorry brains in.
Oh, oh, oh, yeah!
Yeah!
Ha, ha, ha, you get it now?
Hey, buddy.
No need to get men down to shape.
It was just a little disagreement.
I just got here, man.
I'm not even on death row.
Don't let me out.
Four and a half days
have passed since Luffy
and Hancock left the
maiden island of Amazon.
I'm sorry sir it's just
that we're a bit late
sir the headwinds delayed
us but we contacted.
The prison we are late
damn call Hancock and
quickly sir uh lady Hancock
ma 'am we've arrived.
This is crazy they got more ships
here than they did for the buster
call you've Seen a Buster Call it's
amazing you survived i've heard
it said that they're quite terrifying
Ace is Here you're sure yes
although i imagine he's deep
underwater hurry step inside my cloak
Welcome to Inside Town, Bicep of Momonga!
Woah, she's so hearty!
Yep, she sure is!
She's the best in the world!
Beauty is power, she's the queen!
A thousand votes?
No, it's like ten thousand!
Train to the heart, baby!
These men are an affront
to my poor ears, Momonga.
May I please turn them to stone?
I would rather you not.
I dare say you've embarrassed the
Marines enough for one lifetime.
Now about that condition of yours.
Before aiding in his execution, you
wanted to meet Portgas D .A .s, correct?
Let me warn you once more
that, warlord or not,
as a pirate, you're not welcome here.
As a result, before you enter,
they will perform a full
body search They will also
require you to wear sea
prism stone handcuffs inside
They have to ensure that
you don't launch any ill
-fated attempts at rescuing
Ace or any other prisoners
Luffy, they're doing a body check
We'll figure something out, don't worry
Very well, go
What buggy the clown you said
he's missing and what's his power?
Excuse me, sir,
but vice-admiral Momonga and Empress
Hancock of the seven warlords have arrived,
right? I'll greet them
She's great wait, I mean
somebody open the gate
All right, this is it.
Careful in air!
We love you, Hancock!
Have a nice visit!
Silence, imbeciles!
Oh, she's so sexy when she's angry!
Oh let me out i'm dying
in here nobody deserves
this it certainly lives
up to its reputation.
This is quite hellish indeed we've made it
this far but i fear the
worst is ahead of us.
Welcome to my prison
Impel Down oops jump the
gun there it's not well
exactly mine just yet.
I'm the vice warden here
annual well for now at
least it's a pleasure to
meet you vice admiral.
Likewise we've been
expecting you ah and this
must be the pirate
empress my pirate empress.
Perhaps Pass jump the
gun again that's a bit
ambitious i suppose the
dumbass warden is Pass.
Not what i meant the
perfectly competent warden
magellan is waiting in
his office on level four.
He said he would like to meet with
you our vice manager of the jail here
miss domino will be more than happy
to guide you there it seems you're
in a rush empress so allow me to
get this unpleasantness out of the
way if you follow me we'll conduct
our body search and begin the tour.
If you are a new prisoner
we would have you
enter the cell over
there strip off all your
clothes and push you into
an iron pot filled with
boiling water we call
it hell's hot tub it's a
baptism and sanitation
solution all in one very
economical i think we
have quite a number of
celebrity prisoners by
the way as you know fire
fist ace showed up recently
but that's not all.
Jinbe of the Seven
Wardlords is a new addition,
and the former Wardlord Crocodile has
made his residence here for a while now.
For the record,
both are model prisoners that didn't
bat an eye at their little baptism.
And don't worry, we search our
visitors in a private room, after you.
before we start could you please
take off your cloak it would be far
too easy for you to hide something
inside there so i'm afraid you'll
have to leave it behind don't
mistake our thoroughness for mistrust
we simply have a reputation we would
like to uphold and as you can see
on the wall here we have surveillance
transponder snails all over
the prison their video footage is
monitored in one of several security
rooms oh and don't forget these
keep in mind that they're sea prism
stone you call me a visitor here not
a prisoner then you put me in those
be gentle i'm delicate
what happened
it's safe now luffy
wow that was close i was
starting to think i'd just
have to crawl out from there
like a cockroach and hope
for the best that power of
yours is really handy in
a pinch huh even so i'm
afraid that this is as far as
i'll be able to accompany
you they're quite insistent
on placing me in those c
prism stone handcuffs and once
they take my cloak you'll
have nowhere to hide i just
wish i wish i could do more
to help you but oh don't
talk like that you got me
in this place didn't you
that's more than i could
have done alone even though
there's guards everywhere
we made it all this way no
problem i can handle the rest
luffy breaking your brother
out will be challenging
enough but if you get captured
as well who knows what
horrors you might face one
wrong step and you may
never see the light of day
again i know you want to save
ace but this is dangerous
Please take care of yourself, too.
I won't let you down.
You have my word.
Thanks for everything, Hancock.
You're the best.
I won't forget what you've done,
not for the rest of my life.
He just called me by my name.
My real, actual name.
For the first time.
Cool.
Whatever works for you, Hammock.
Can I get snap control over here, Hammock?
Hey, Hammock, what are you doing?
Hey Hancock.
My life is finally complete.
I can die happy.
Hey, you can turn that lady back now!
I should be fine up here.
Say it, Luffy.
Say my name again.
This is taking too long?
This situation is unprecedented.
She's probably just being thorough.
Oh, that's so naughty!
Get your mind out of the gutter, damn it!
Uh,
Vice-Wordant Hannibal,
we're not getting any visuals from the
surveillance down in the examination room.
Is there something going on
in there we don't know about?
Huh?
Domino, something wrong in there?
We have completed the body search sir
Scratch that last report
everything is fine here.
I hope I didn't cause a problem sir.
Did the exam take too long?
No
Everything's fine on our end, too.
I See that your guests are treated
as poorly as your prisoners here?
Surely an empress
deserves better than this!
It is a pity but in Impel Down we can't
afford to make exceptions to the rules.
I wonder why I can't shake
this strange feeling.
Lead the way!
Ah, yes, if you'll let
me in front, please!
Or just go that way.
Before we visit Ace,
we'll take this elevator to what
we call the burning heat floor.
Where we'll stop by the
Warden Magellan's office.
Fair warning, as the name
implies, it's quite hot there.
Luffy be bold but be safe.
Bye Hancock!
Thank you.
He really does love me.
He's Empress Hancock. What's wrong?
Do you need mouth to mouth?
Are you ill?
You were fine just a
moment ago. What happened?
Okay, not sure where to
take things from here.
Hancock said Ace is probably underwater.
Looks like that elevator
might head down a long way.
Oh yeah, the fever card
might come in handy.
Looks like they grabbed dinner, too.
Open the hatch!
Nice work.
Get it to the fridge and we'll be done.
We found him!
That's buggy.
The clown prisoner from level
one community cell number
four in the hallway in front
of solitary cell number 22?
Stupid snail, this is all your fault!
You blew it, buggy old don't come crying
to us when they're torturing you to death.
Serves you right, you dummy!
Yeah, he'll wish he was dead for sure.
Oh, here come the Bligotti.
Happy hunting.
Make him suffer.
The fever guard keeps leading
me down, but now what?
Guess I'm out of stairs.
All right, men.
We're looking for prisoner 8200. What?
The stupid clown?
No one knew he had Devil Fruit powers.
You got the handcuffs?
Yeah, we're good.
Let's move.
Split up and flank him.
Cool. I made it. Hurry!
Wonder what's up.
So all of these are prison cells?
What's that? Huh?
I gotta get moving.
Huh?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Buddy, slow down.
Hold on a second.
Kind of busy.
Yeah, that's what it looks like, but how
the heck did you get out of your cell?
Hey, what's going on?
I didn't get out.
I came in from the outside.
Well, bye. Hey, hold up.
There's no way that's the truth.
Uh-huh, it's so true.
You don't look like a jailer.
So who are you and why
the hell are you here?
He's not behind bars, so maybe it's true.
You guys have some really bad attitudes.
Wait a sec.
Any of you know where I can find Ace?
Uh, Ace?
Wait, Ace?
You mean, him?
The guy on death row?
That's the one.
I came here to bust him out of this place.
Yeah, good luck with that.
We don't get a lot of info down here,
but I heard they just brought him in.
If that's true and he is here,
then he's got to be on level five.
No way you're getting down there.
You're screwed, pal.
That's the floor where
they hold all the prisoners
with the bounty of a
hundred million or more.
Level five, huh?
Oh, and by the way, pal,
why you here you think you could run to
the jailer's room and pick us up some keys?
Yeah, buddy.
Wouldn't be no trouble, right?
This has got to be destiny, man.
I mean, what else would
bring us together like this?
It's like you were born
to set us free, right?
What are those things?
Stop the body!
I don't like him! Run! Hurry!
They're gonna kill you!
I take him back!
I like you!
Right side!
And left side!
You're tight!
How you like that, suckers?
You can cut me all you want!
I ate the chop-chop fruits!
Straw rats!
What the hell are you doing here?
Oh, buggy.
Thanks for reminding me why I hate you!
I see prison hasn't made
you any less annoying.
Speaking of, guess that King of the
Pirates thing ain't working out too well.
I came here on my own.
Only dumb people like you get
caught and thrown in jail.
Say what?
You threw yourself in jail and
you're calling me the dumb one?
You must have known I was here.
That's the real reason.
You're broken, isn't it?
To save me.
I'm not into you, weirdo.
Just shut up and get
the hell out of my way.
I told Hancock I'd take
care of myself and you
got all these stupid axe
monkeys chasing after me.
Oh, I see.
This is all about you, is it?
This is supposed to be a cinch.
I called it Buggy's Peaceful Escape Plan.
Does this look peaceful to you?
Who cares?
They're surrounding us, damn it.
I hate this.
Hey, should we just beat those things up?
Easy for you to say you
haven't been tortured.
Oh, how my delicate body has suffered
from the blows of these monsters.
Why can't they think I'm
running away in the first place?
Yeah, but I wasn't
planning to lose. Right.
Clearly you've thought this out.
I'm on a mission here.
My cover's already been blown, so
I gotta get this done in a hurry.
You know, that's the number one reason
why I hate you and that redhead so much.
Both of you are always so optimistic
in the worst way possible.
Alright, fine.
I'll go along with your crazy plan.
It's not like I have a choice!
Shhh!
Time for my specialty!
Causing chaos!
Works for me!